System call.
Generate Luminous Element.
it.
Wow, look at all this stuff.
Hurry, let's find our
swords and get out of here.
There They are?
I can leave the room if
you two need a minute.
Sorry.
I don't get it.
I thought the Integrity Knights were
enough to stop the forces of darkness.
Is the church building an army?
It's not that.
It's the opposite, in fact.
The church brought all this here
to make sure no one builds one.
What would be the point of that? Simple.
The church doesn't want
people rising up against it.
Or, to be more specific,
administrator doesn't.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Time's a-wasted.
Yeah, right. I'm coming.
Maybe we should take some armor.
What do you think?
We never fought in it before,
so it might slow us down.
It's better if we stick to what we know.
We could use a fresh
set of clothes, though.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's hard to say it.
On the way, I'm going to step in.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know what you're
doing to tell you about it.
I don't know if you're gonna have a rule.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
First element!
Charge him!
Futile.
Kirito! You hit?
No. I'm good.
That was way too close.
Let's go.
System call.
Uh-oh, not good.
That's no typical spell.
It's perfect weapon control.
Enhance armament.
That bow's awesome!
Holy hell, I wonder what it was before.
We have bigger things to worry about.
I last bathed in the conflagration
bow's fire two years ago.
Now I summon the fire again
to deal with you sinners.
You have the skills to match Sir Eldrie,
but what you did to him is unforgivable.
Instead of fighting
like knights with honor,
you corrupted his mind and led him
astray with the Dark Arts. What?
It was nothing like that.
You're wrong, Sir Knight.
All we did was remind him of his
life before he became a knight.
What are you babbling about?
We knights do not have a past.
We have always been Integrity Knights.
Our existence begins when we
are summoned from the heavens.
I should burn you criminals to ash,
but my orders are to capture you alive.
Unfortunately, I have unleashed
the conflagration bow.
Now one of your arms will
most likely be incinerated.
That bow's going to do serious damage now.
Any ideas?
I got a feeling you can't
rapid-fire with that.
If I'm lucky and block the
first shot, you charge him.
That's not reassuring.
I'm ready.
System call!
Generate cryogenic elements!
Disharge!
Fool!
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Kirito!
Now's your chance! Go get him!
Do not toy with me.
Now what?
You have to think about what
you're putting behind your strikes.
What do you think I should
put behind mine, then?
That's something you're going
to have to figure out yourself.
That's it.
She's all that matters.
I'm here for her, and
nothing will stop me.
Blue Rose Sword, lend me your power.
Please, give me the
strength to keep going!
Please, you're cold and sharp.
Forged since creation by freezing cold
blizzards at the top of the End Mountains.
You can't let these weak flames melt.
You, now!
You're finished!
Oh, my God.
Boy, that first skill
you used, what was it?
It's of the Aincrad style.
A two-hit strike.
Vertical arc.
And you what was your
skill Kirito are you okay
yeah i'm good i healed
the worst burns myself
What's my skill it's
Aincrad too one of the
defense skills it's called spinning shield
I thought i had seen it all i've been from
one end of this realm to the other And
beyond and yet there are styles i've never
seen and skills i've never encountered
I can tell there is much
discipline in you and
you have spent years of
training in your style
Earlier i accused you
of using the dark arts
to corrupt Sir Eldrie
i know now that i was
mistaken.
I would be honored to know your names.
I am Eugeo, the swordsman.
Kirito the swordsman.
On the 50th floor, in the great hall of
ghostly light, Integrity Knights wait.
Should you pass me,
they will not take you prisoner.
They have orders to
extinguish your lives instead.
If you charge them head-on
like you did me just now,
you will most certainly meet your end.
Whoa, hang on a sec.
Why tell us?
Whose side are you on?
I failed to carry out
Administrator's order.
I shall be stripped of my armor and
divine object, the proof of my knighthood.
Then I shall be frozen for eternity.
I do not wish to suffer the indignity.
Therefore, I want you to end my life.
There is no need to hesitate.
After all, you defeated me fairly,
using your splendid skills.
By the way, my name is
Tiese Elbert Synthesis 7.
You're Tiese Elbert?
Yu-Gi-Oh, you're the one who took her.
A fair battle.
Dignity?
You want to die with honor, do you?
Do you?
Where was your honor when you
chained up an 11-year-old girl?
You tied her to your
dragon and took her away.
Dying with honor is too good for you!
I'm right. I am.
Aren't I?
You heard what he said.
He's not going to fight back.
You don't kill a defenseless person.
I know, but...
he came to my village and took Alice!
You know the church messes
with these guys' heads.
I doubt he remembers being in
Rulid, or taking Alice away.
It's true, ain't it?
You don't remember.
It is as your companion says.
I am a knight.
I protect.
I would never kidnap a child,
much less chain them to my dragon.
If I did, I do not remember.
What are you talking about?
It happened eight years ago!
Old man, I mean Tiese Elbert.
Eight years ago, you were guarding
the border of North Norlinggarth.
Do you remember that?
I do.
District 7 in North Norlinggarth was mine.
I used to patrol the borderlands.
That is, until eight years ago.
For some reason, the church rewarded me.
I received this armor and was given the
duty to guard the central cathedral.
Do you remember what the
church rewarded you for?
I'll tell you why you don't.
You were on a mission to steal his friend.
She's called Alice Synthesis 30 now.
As soon as you brought her back here,
Administrator rewarded you all right.
She also erased your
memory of what you did,
because she can't have
you remembering her.
You told us before that
Integrity Knights have no past.
Your lives begin when you're summoned
from heaven, but that's a lie.
That's something the Pontifex
tells all the Knights,
right after they come
to, and you know why?
To help explain why
none of you can remember
anything before becoming
an Integrity Knight.
She doesn't want you to have
any memories, not even one.
And she doesn't stop with the
memories of your human life.
She takes the ones you
have of other knights, too.
The ones you brought to her to get turned.
If a sinner you brought
in for judgment showed up
as a knight the next day
and you remembered them,
there'd be chaos.
But I would remember. I would.
Like I said, Administrator
stole your memories.
And then, she forced
absolute loyalty on you.
Then she turned you into a knight.
But you're human, just like us.
Human?
And having my memory manipulated?
By the Pontifex?
Impossible.
Absurd. No, boy.
You are the one who is mistaken here.
Look, try to remember something.
Anything at all.
I bet there's an image or a feeling there.
Something so precious to
you, no art can erase it.
From the time I first ascended,
I keep having the same dream.
A delicate hand shaking me awake,
and on one finger, a silver ring.
And when I do wake up,
there's no one there.
Whoever that hand belongs to
is someone special to you.
Administrator stole your memory of him.
What you do next is up to you.
You can go back to Administrator
and accept your punishment.
Or you can heal yourself
and come after us.
Your call.
All these stairs.
How far up are we now?
The next floor is the 29th.
At the rate we're going, we'll reach
the 50th floor in half an hour.
Should we just charge in?
Good question.
You think of everything.
After seeing how that last
dude fought, I got a theory.
Combo attacks seem to
throw these knights off.
It's like they never had
a deal with them before.
If it's one-on-one and we could get
up close, I think we'd have a chance.
But that knight said there's a bunch
up there and they're ready for us.
That's going to make things harder.
You're right.
Perhaps we should avoid them.
Find another way up.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Cardinal said these stairs
were the only way up,
so we're going to have to deal with them.
Even if we did find a way around, we'd
have to face them on the way back down.
We should deal with those knights now.
Our new special skill should help.
That's right.
Perfect weapon control.
Yup.
Maybe if we use it when we charge in, we
can take a bunch out before they can react.
With any luck, our first
strike will get them all.
Actually, we should talk about that.
I don't think I'll be much help.
My version of perfect
weapon control isn't a
direct attack like that
Integrity Knights was.
What?
You're kidding.
Uh-uh.
Not based on the command
Cardinal wrote for me.
I mean, I guess in the end
it's my fault for imagining it.
Well, let me check it out and
see what's up with it. Okay.
Yeah, you're right.
It might not be quick enough
for a surprise attack.
Still, it should come in handy
as long as you use it right.
Plus, it looks like it complements
my perfect control art.
Really?
Can I see what yours is like?
Nah, I don't want to spoil the surprise.
Let's get going. Huh?
We see you. Come out.
They're children.
I don't know.
Oh oh oh oh?
I don't know how life goes on?
Oh everything turns to ash to ash!
My life is the path I see.
My pain and pain are hurt.
And everything turns to dust to dust.
When I die,
when I die,
when I die?
Next time, The Relentless Knight.